Contact Information

Email

ardatila13@gmail.com

Address

14/C Lotz Karoly Street, Pécs, Baranya, Hungary, 7633

Phone

- +905333115503 /
- +36205288655

Date of birth

Nov 13, 1998

Nationality

Turkish

Link

https://tr.linkedin.com/in/arda-burak-atila-a5a126141

https://github.com/archel v

Skills

Teamwork Problem-Solving

Python

Postman

Bootstrap

SQL

GitHub

Linux

API

API Testing

Adobe Photoshop

Languages

English

Intermediate

Turkish

Native

Hungarian

Elementary

Arda Burak Atila

Software Developer

I study computer science at University of Pécs. I have focused on front end development, data mining and back enddevelopment since 2018. The first programing skill that I learn is Python and also I have been improving my java skill. Therefore I have some projects which are related to robotics and *parnote works. I always looking to learn new skills, take on extra responsibilities, and grow professionally. I experienced in training and mentoring new members of staff. I have worked in busy, pressurized environments where high standards are expected. Also I saw your projects and I believe will improve my skills this company.



Experience

Istanbul, Turkey Jul 2021 - Aug 2021 Software Developer

Crede Consulting & Data Sevices

I delivered a small software collecting data from free test using Java and Regular Expressions.

Istanbul, Turkey Jul 2021 - Aug 2021 Software Developer

Trio Mobil

I used Postman for API testing. I learned GET, POST, PULL and DELETE methods. I learned how to send requests to API. I performed API testing with the Axios method over Javascript

Education

Hungary, Pécs Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

Hungary, Pécs Sep 2018 - Jun 2019

Turkey, Istanbul Sep 2014 - Jun 2017 Computer Science Bsc.

University of Pécs

Average Score: 4.05

Preparatory School
International Studies Center

High School

Private Atasehir Okyanus Science High School

Projects

ParNote Project, Pécs

In September 2020 as the ParNote team, we wanted to take the ParNote project, which we started as a lecture project at the university, to the next stage and created as a real project. ParNote is a note app based on it, but unlike many other note apps, you can collaborate with other people by inviting them to your notes, share your personal notes with other people and see theirs too. With its simple interface and stylish design, ParNote invites you to write notes..

Bootsrap, JS, Kotlin and MariaDB

Source code: https://github.com/ParNote-App

Certifications & Courses

- Introduction to Git and Github, Coursera
- Python, Coursera
- Adobe After Effect, Coursera
- B2, English Certificate, Busuu

